ruthlessincome.com 2014-02-21

# The Last Goldmine

**Logged in as:** Last Goldmine Guest

The Last Goldmine Privacy Policy

The privacy and confidentiality of our members and prospects is upheld with the highest consideration. The Last Goldmine is committed to respecting your privacy. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This policy will let you know the following: 

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from me? 

2\. What are cookies and how they are used by The Last Goldmine? 

3\. How is my information used? 

4\. Who is collecting my information? 

5\. With whom will my information be shared? 

6\. How can I access, update or delete my information? 

7\. What does "opt-out" mean? 

8\. What else should I know about my privacy? 

9\. Other legal notices. 

**1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from me?**   
On some The Last Goldmine Web pages you can make requests and/or receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are your name, e-mail address and standard contact information, including addresses and phone numbers. We may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with the services we provide and contact preferences. Wherever The Last Goldmine collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

**2\. What are cookies and how are they used by The Last Goldmine?**   
The Last Goldmine may place Internet cookies on your hard drive. Internet cookies are small files that may be placed on your hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies are used to (a) remind us of who you are in order to deliver you better service; (b) estimate our audience size by determining repeat usage of the Web site to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior; (c) track your progress and entries in promotions, sweepstakes and contests, if any; and (d) measure certain traffic patterns for use as a research tool to understand how our users’ habits are similar or different from one another. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. By not accepting cookies, some Web pages may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information. 

The Last Goldmine may also collect IP addresses (the Internet address of a computer) to track a user's session while the user remains anonymous. We analyze this data for certain trends in statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there. In general, we do not link your IP addresses to anything personally identifiable to you. 

**3\. How is my information used?**   
The Last Goldmine will not provide your personally identifiable information to others without your consent. The information you provide will be used to support your customer relationship with The Last Goldmine. Your information may be shared with agents, contractors or business partners for the purpose of performing services for The Last Goldmine. 

We want to help you quickly find information on The Last Goldmine and alert you to specific offers, updated information, and other new products and services from The Last Goldmine. Accordingly, we may send you email, direct mailings or contact you by telephone about our various products and services or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply "opt-out" by the means provided for in the mailings or by contacting support@champsites.com. 

Notwithstanding, The Last Goldmine does research on our users' demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us during your use of the The Last Goldmine Web site. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. The Last Goldmine may share this aggregated data with others. 

From time to time affiliates of The Last Goldmine may have special offers for customers of The Last Goldmine. In such cases you will be given an opportunity to "opt-in" and receive additional information about those offers. In such cases by electing to receive information from The Last Goldmine affiliates your information will be transferred to those third parties. The information practices of those third parties are not covered by this privacy statement. 

**4\. Who is collecting my information?**   
When you are on an The Last Goldmine site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with The Last Goldmine alone, unless specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than The Last Goldmine or an agent for The Last Goldmine, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service or purchasing those particular goods. 

Please be aware that The Last Goldmine advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Web sites linked to The Last Goldmine either through advertisements or other hyperlinks are not covered by this privacy statement and The Last Goldmine shall have no liability for the actions and policies of these third parties. 

**5\. With whom does The Last Goldmine share my information?**   
We may share the personal data you provide with other The Last Goldmine agents, contractors or our business partners for the purposes of performing services for The Last Goldmine. The Last Goldmine also may share aggregated data with others. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. We also believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Access, or as otherwise required by law. Except as provided above or in the event of a merger, consolidation, or sale of all or substantially all of The Last Goldmine's assets, we will not share any of your information with any third party without your permission. 

**6\. How do I access, update or delete my information?**   
You can request the individual information that The Last Goldmine has collected about you, correct factual inaccuracies in your information, remove personal information from The Last Goldmine's data bases and/or update your personal information by contacting support@champsites.com. 

**7\. What does "opt-out" mean?**   
To "opt-out" means that you have notified The Last Goldmine that we no longer have permission to use your information to contact you regarding promotions of other The Last Goldmine products. For example, when we send you information on a new product, you will be given the opportunity to "opt-out" of receiving such information in the future. 

**8\. What else should I know about my privacy?** Third party Internet sites and services accessible through The Last Goldmine have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. The Last Goldmine has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please be careful and responsible online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your information, The Last Goldmine cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information through the transmission process and you do so at your own risk. 

**9\. Other Legal Notices.**   
Any dispute over privacy is subject to this privacy policy and our Terms of Access including limitations on damages and application of the law of the State of New York. If you have any concern about your privacy in connection with this policy, please send us a thorough description to support@thelastgoldmine.com, and we will try to resolve it. We may post a revised privacy policy on our site. Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the privacy notice in effect at the time of use. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. 

**The Last Goldmine  
PO Box 4084 Monroe, CT 06468   
support@thelastgoldmine.com **   

* * *

Need To Access Your Membership?

Please enter your email address and your Last Goldmine password to access your account. If you did not get your password by email after signing up, click the " Password " tab above and we will send it to you right now!

This is an advertisement.  
---|---
